{
    "subject": "resource/Neal_Doughty",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Evansville,_Indiana",
    "human_readable": "Neal Doughty was born in Evansville, Indiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.906525194644928,
            "question": "Where was Neal Doughty born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8629428744316101,
            "question": "In what state was Neal Doughty born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722774088382721,
            "question": "Do you know any facts about Indiana besides Neal Doughty's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6783089637756348,
            "question": "What city is associated with Neal Doughty's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5883165597915649,
            "question": "What is the significance of Neal Doughty's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5828275084495544,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Evansville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5260440707206726,
            "question": "What is Neal Doughty known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3824063539505005,
            "question": "Is there anything else notable about Evansville, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27252230048179626,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Neal Doughty's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26554247736930847,
            "question": "How did Neal Doughty's upbringing potentially influence his life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Neal Doughty was born in Evansville, Indiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5093_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Neal Doughty's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5093_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else notable about Evansville, Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5093_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Neal Doughty known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5093_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5093_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Neal Doughty being born in Evansville, Indiana, including his birthdate and city of birth. This information supports the triple that Neal Doughty was indeed born in Evansville, Indiana."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references stating that Neal Doughty was born in Evansville, Indiana. Therefore, the statement \"Neal Doughty was born in Evansville, Indiana\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}